<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Cavan Klinsky</title>
 <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2013-09-15T21:34:31-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://klinskyc.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Cavan Klinsky</name>
 </author>
 
 
 <entry>
   <title>Fantasy Football Week 1</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/Fantasy-Football-Week-1"/>
   <updated>2013-09-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/Fantasy-Football-Week-1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a little different then my normal stuff but I enjoy fantasy football (and football in general) and I
think it&amp;rsquo;s worth posting, if just for my own sake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year I joined &lt;a href=&quot;http://reddit.com/r/narffl&quot;&gt; NARFFL &lt;/a&gt; reddit&amp;rsquo;s fantasy football league, I then promptly
missed the draft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I remember the next day and logged in, the autodraft had picked me this (This is my current line-up,
substitue Tampa Bay with Knile Davis and Julian Edelman with Ronnie Hillman). This league awards 1 point per
reception.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fflineup-week2.png&quot; alt=&quot;My Fantasy Football Team&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an auto-draft this wasn&amp;rsquo;t the worst thing ever&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pros&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An amazing QB in Peyton Manning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 decent rb in Ray Rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good WR and TE depth (too many TEs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Cons&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monte Ball isn&amp;rsquo;t an RB2 or an RB anything, this is a serious problem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have way too many TEs and not enough RBs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have one ok running back (notice a pattern)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;Before the Game&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to be smart I dropped the RB Knile Davis and picked up the Tampa Bay defense because they were playing the Jets. ( the
Jets are my favorite team but it was worth taking the opportunityt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The First Game&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Week1_Matchup.png&quot; alt=&quot;Week 1 Matchup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week went pretty well, Peyton Manning had a record setting game and Ray Rice and my WRs, TE and Kicked
 had solid performances. My favorite part was that Tampa Bay managed to lose to the Jets and they still put up
 more points than the Bronco&amp;rsquo;s D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The only bad thing (and it&amp;rsquo;s a large bad thing) is that Monte Ball put up 2.4 points as it became evident
 that Denver really is making the game a running back by committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;For Next Week&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; I need to fix my RB situation, I can probably pawn off Brandon Myers, the NYG Tight End.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Have 13 Users And I Am Ecstatic</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/I-Have-13-Users-And-I-Am-Ecstatic"/>
   <updated>2013-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/I-Have-13-Users-And-I-Am-Ecstatic</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After spending the last few months working on and off on a large project (more on that over the summer), I was
feeling burnt out from constantly getting stuck on large-scale bugs. In response to this, I decided to make
something incredibly simple in an area that I had never worked in before. After spending a few minutes googling
how to make a rss feed out of a twitter profile I decided to simplify an already simple process and make a chrome
extension, something I had never done before. After half an hour, The result was &lt;a href=&quot;https://chr
ome.google.com/webstore/detail/twitter2rss/obnmifkmfdnijcnmhacachchiikikchb&quot; &gt;this&lt;/a&gt;, a sub20 lines of code
chrome extension that made a rss feed out of any twitter-page. I paid the five dollar publishing fee and went
to bed, happy that I had finally finished something, albeit tiny. After one week, I checked the stats and saw
something that astounded me, the weekly users were up to 13. I was surprised, why would anyone want to install an
extension that had so little use? Honestly, I still have no idea. All I know is that I got more users for 30 minutes
of work than I did over two months and I&amp;rsquo;m happy about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another note the Chrome Web Store is a Mecca for lean-startupers
(is that a word?). It allows for fast iterations and feedback in an app-store environment that already has a
userbase, free advertising and users without the restrictions of the Apple or Google Play stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the extension &lt;a href=&quot;https://chr
ome.google.com/webstore/detail/twitter2rss/obnmifkmfdnijcnmhacachchiikikchb&quot; &gt; here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Interesting Attempt At Getting User Signups</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/An-Interesting-Attempt-At-Getting-User-Signups"/>
   <updated>2013-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/An-Interesting-Attempt-At-Getting-User-Signups</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I think almost anyone on the internet has seen this message&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &amp;ldquo;Log In With Facebook (Twitter, G+) To View&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I do not think I&amp;rsquo;m alone in that I leave the page as soon as I see one of them.
Normally these messages all come in the same form but today I saw something clever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Facebook_Signup.png&quot; alt=&quot;Are You Over 13?&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of just presenting it in the normal we-just-want-your-information way, this site is able
to offer a (shaky) justification while still forcing user signups. The whole idea behind it is a farce
(the opacity is so low that you can see the image anyways) but it stil is an interesting way to
increase user signups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can view the live example &lt;a href =&quot;http://www.lulztruck.org/actually-a-good-point&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How The Mighty Have Fallen</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/How-The-Mighty-Have-Fallen"/>
   <updated>2013-03-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/How-The-Mighty-Have-Fallen</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I recently happened to see this Time Magazine cover.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.timeinc.net/time/magazine/archive/covers/2002/1101020415_400.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Time Magazine Cover&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing that caught my eye wasn&amp;rsquo;t any of the content but some words in the bottom right corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/AOLTime.png&quot; alt=&quot;AOL Keyword: Time&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe that a magazine as large as Time would ever put their AOL Keyword on the front page.
From Jan 31, 2000 to August 14, 2006 Time had it on every issue. This just goes to show how much power and visibility AOL had
and then lost on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can You Imagine Time having a Facebook or Twitter link there?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Experiment</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/The-Experiment"/>
   <updated>2013-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/The-Experiment</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;The Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent years I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading more and more news online and fewer and fewer books. Instead of sitting down
with a novel or a history book I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending that time on Reddit and Hacker News. It&amp;rsquo;s not just me, all
over the world people are reading less. Despite the high quality content on a site like Hacker News,
I get a lot less out of an hour online then I do from an hour of reading. I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading more news online because
simply, it&amp;rsquo;s easier to find and consume. So I set out to fix this problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The (Possible) Solution&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started with a Google Doc spreadsheet, a bunch of  HN and Reddit threads of recommended books, and a random number generator.
My process was quite simple, any book that sounded interesting was put in the spreadsheet. After I was done trawling
through all the different threads I had a list of about 20 books that I wanted to read, each of them correlating
with a cell number in the spreadsheet. Using a random number generator I picked out 3 numbers and their corresponding
books. I then, for the first time in years, actually read all of them in a short time frame. After completing each
one I would enter the pages and a short paragraph of my thoughts on the book into the spreadsheet. The enjoyment
of entering the finished books into the spreadsheet compelled me to read more and more and so far I&amp;rsquo;ve read more in the
past two months than I had read in the past year. Is this method revolutionary? Almost surely not, but it helped me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can view the spreadsheet &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0As9wx2iv9PqudEN5S3FuT0NJeHNhSldKSmoyV3dCeWc&amp;usp=sharing&quot;&gt; here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m curious to know whether this method works for anyone else. Make sure to send me a message on twitter if you try it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Apple's Future</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/Apple%27s-Future"/>
   <updated>2013-01-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/Apple's-Future</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;A Non-Expert&amp;rsquo;s Opinion on Apple&amp;rsquo;s Future&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dust of Job’s death is settled and the scoreboard speaks for itself. During Steve Job’s two-part twenty-four year tenure with Apple the world was changed.  Job’s innovations are innumerable, from the Apple I to the IPad, Jobs has created computer revolutions and has moved forward the world in which we live in. Apple without Jobs shows a stark contrast, without Jobs Apple has a history of creating forgotten misguided products like the Macintosh Performa or the Apple Newton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Job’s death Apple has been running on the fumes of his genius, any attempts to go off his path have led to overhyped misstep after overhyped misstep. Siri, a technology that was supposed to change the world and one of the first things to come out of Apple post Jobs, has been a novelty at best and broken at worst. It is only one in a long growing line of failing products. Apple Maps, a recently made competitor to Google Maps, has been a flop. In a rare apology from a company that until recently has had nothing to be sorry about, CEO Tim Cook wrote “We fell short on Apple Maps.”  This is putting it lightly; Apple Maps has been repeatedly called a “complete failure” and led to the ousting of mobile software head Scott Forstall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple’s competitors are catching up to and surpassing Apple’s growth. With the new additions of the Kindle Fire, Windows Surface, and the Google Nexus 7 along with many other smartphones and tablets, the smartphone and tablet market is getting crowded and Apple is beginning to be squeezed out by low priced competitors. In 2012, Samsung, one of Apple’s major competitors, gained three times as much market share as Apple in the smartphone market. In the tablet market, Apple’s market share has dropped from 90% two years ago to only 44% today. The new growth opportunities created by the fall of former smartphone giants Research in Motion and Nokia is not being seized by Apple but by its competitors, Google, Amazon, and Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another worrying trend for Apple is its seeming reliance on new hardware innovations to acquire customers. For a company that made it’s name with new innovations in both  software and hardware, its recent software innovations have been few and far between. Even when they do innovate, like with the aforementioned Siri and Maps, the innovations are almost totally malfunctioning failures. Jobs, in his lifetime, refused to accept anything less than perfection. After the launch of MobileMe, one of the few blemishes in Jobs’ tenure at Apple, Jobs gathered the MobileMe team into a room and said “You&amp;rsquo;ve tarnished Apple&amp;rsquo;s reputation, you should hate each other for having let each other down.”  If this was what Jobs did after such a small blemish, imagine how he would have reacted to the full-scale meltdown that was Apple Maps. Jobs would have, at least in one former Apple employees opinion, “lost his mind.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This dearth of new must-have technology is allowing competitors like Google and Amazon to catch back up. Since September Apple’s stock price has been down 35%. Apple’s most recent quarter report was four billion dollars short of estimated revenue and Apple lost its spot as most valuable company.   Apple needs to innovate or die and currently they are dying. Apple is slowly starting to fade into obscurity.  As Edmund Burke put it “those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it.” Apple can only sink from here, don’t go down with the ship.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What I Use</title>
   <link href="http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/What-I-Use"/>
   <updated>2013-01-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://klinskyc.github.io/posts/What-I-Use</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this Inaugural Post I&amp;rsquo;ll take briefly about what I use on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Gadgets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Mid 2012 13 Inch MacBook Pro (Non Retina)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.pcworld.com/reviews/graphics/products/uploaded/apple_13inch_macbook_pro29ghz_core_i5_mid_2012_1220659_g1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
This is my true workhorse and everything I do ends up on this at some point.
 Before I bought it I was torn between this model and the 13 Inch Macbook Air and
 while I am sure I would say the exact opposite if I had gone with the Air I feel
 like I made the right decision. I think it represents a nice compromise between portability, computing power,
 and price. I carry it around every day and I have no complaints about it&amp;rsquo;s weight. Albeit from a few scuffs and a little dirt it has held up well to pretty rough daily treatment. If only chargers faired as well.
  I do miss having a 24 inch screen but less than I thought I would due to a makeshift solution (more on that in a moment).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;IPhone 3GS&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.pcworld.com/reviews/graphics/products/uploaded/116744_g2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;
Since I got this in 2009 I&amp;rsquo;ve slowly watched it go from top of the line to barely supported
 while giving me no problems all the while. My apps still run and my music still plays so I have still have
 not seen any compelling reason to upgrade. I&amp;rsquo;m still running 5.0.1 as my 3GS doesn&amp;rsquo;t get many of the new features of 6.0 and Siri.
 I think I would have upgraded already if not for wonderful jailbreak apps like SBSettings that I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like going through the process of reinstalling again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Early 2009 24 Inch iMac&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;http://cache.gawkerassets.com/assets/images/gizmodo/2009/03/newimac.jpg&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
My main computer for 3 years, it now sits on my desk serving niche purposes. It&amp;rsquo;s main use now is as a hacked together second monitor for my MBP. I have yet to find a working, practical
solution to use it as a true second monitor so I&amp;rsquo;ve just been using teleport(like synergy) and
Soundflow to almost make it one. I normally use it to show Movies, Chat, or pdfs, documents and
websites that I need to constantly reference. Since its on 10.6 it&amp;rsquo;s used for any Powerpc
app or non-updated intel app. I also use it to run .bat files. For these things it works pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;iPad 2 3G&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://cdn1.sbnation.com/products/large/126/1300358445apple_ipad2_black_01.jpg?1312559901&quot;  height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
I bought this in 2011 to use as my portable community and it served its job ok before being replaced by my MBP.
For anything non-intensive like web-browsing, email, reddit, or reading, the iPad performs beautifully.
The cracks begin to show when you try to do anything more.
Even with a bluetooth keyboard, writing anything longer than an email is slow and unfun.
It gets even worse when I try to do actual work on it. Despite trying almost every native solution
(I never tried ssh) the iPad never came close to being as good as a real computer for coding, image editing,
or anything else. If I can&amp;rsquo;t install ruby or git on a computer then I can&amp;rsquo;t use it as real computer.
The iPad is currently being used as a dedicated ebook reader and other light browsing and for this it performs admirably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Software&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;BBEdit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://cdn-static.zdnet.com/i/story/60/19/010594/bbedit-10-screenshot-ogrady.png&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
One of the oldest text editors for mac, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been using this for that long. I switched to this from TextMate a few years ago because of it&amp;rsquo;s overflowing features.
For something that was supposed to be barebones it really has everything. The two main reasons I switched I because I liked the layout and it&amp;rsquo;s ftp support more than TextMate.
I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been thinking about trying out Sublime Text 2 but I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like leaving this old friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Terminal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://peppoj.net/wp-content/uploads/2010/07/512-Terminal.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not much to say here, just the vanilla Mac OSX Terminal.No complaints, always works as expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Google Chrome&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.blogcdn.com/www.engadget.com/media/2011/04/chrome-logo-2011-04-27.jpg&quot;  height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;
Once again pretty standard stuff. I&amp;rsquo;ve found this to be (at least for me) the fastest full-featured browser.
 I&amp;rsquo;ve found the sync feature to be invaluable along with plugins like Adblock and LastPass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Sparrow&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.gawkerassets.com/img/17tf13akoui94png/original.png&quot;  height=&quot;400&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
Although it&amp;rsquo;s been bought by google and discontinued I still use this as my desktop email client.
 It does everything I could ask for and it does it well. If I had to choose one feature it would be its top-notch
 multi-email account integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Dropbox&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://twimg0-a.akamaihd.net/profile_images/480262550/box.png&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;
While this is another standard, I can&amp;rsquo;t even count the number of times it&amp;rsquo;s backups have saved me from forgetting
to print or transfer something. It also makes a wonderful way to share files.
 My only modification is that I&amp;rsquo;ve set up symlinks to allow me to back up other directories not in the dropbox folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Google Docs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://edudemic.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/GoogleDocs.jpg&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;
I have the entire Microsoft Office Suite on my computer but I find myself almost never using it due to this
wonderful Office replacement. It fulfills all my needs while doing it in its own lightweight, cloud backuped way.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>